Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to the CBS
Evening News. My name is Tim Dylan. I
want to first start by thanking Barry
Weiss for giving me the opportunity to
sit here with you at the iconic CBS news
desk and deliver the news. CBS is a
great American institution.
I also want to speak directly to people
who feel that there may be some changes
coming at CBS or that the network isn't
going to be recognizable. Nothing could
be further from the truth. Here at CBS,
we have a journalistic commitment to
integrity,
giving you both sides or all sides of
every issue that matters to you. Barry
is committed to delivering fearless,
unbiased journalism,
and she is incredibly aware of of what a
shill you people think she is. But she
is not
she is not a shill and nor am I. I want
to thank the Ellison family. I want to
thank Paramount. I want to thank um
everybody who invested severely in me
and Barry and the whole team at the free
press. The investments made were
intense. They were severe. And I want to
thank everyone who took hundreds of
millions, if not billions of dollars
to make sure that you are getting
fearless,
unbiased news coverage from a team
that's only agenda is the truth. Our
only agenda is the truth.
That is the biggest thing that we are
trying to do here. We are not trying to
come on here and spin and say,
"Hey,
hey, you anti-semite pigs, eat your
slop." We're not trying to say that.
We're trying to say the world is very
big and there's a lot of people that
have a lot of opinions that need to be
corrected. And here at CBS News, we are
going to devote every waking minute of
our day to correcting all of you very
nicely.
You're barely going to notice it's
happening. You're barely going to notice
we're there.
So for Tim Dylan,
and
the thing about the beard which makes it
so difficult
is that it really does I have sensitive
skin. It's very hard to speak in this
beard. We got this uh what is this? A
hidic Jew costume at Spirit Halloween.
>> A rabbi.
>> This is a rabbi costume at Spirit
Halloween.
Um to of course, by the way, it's a
happy day. It's a great day. We're
celebrating this day. It's a national
holiday. It's I believe the day that the
free press, Barry Weiss's blog, was
bought for uh $1 trillion. It is now uh
valued at what prochina is valued at.
and she will be taking over CBS news.
So, our the oldest and most vulnerable
members of our society will be getting
news directly from Barry Weiss, who's a
friend of mine who I like. I tend to
like these types. I really do. And uh
and I enjoy her and I wish her well and
I'm wishing her the best. I know that it
seems like we're poking fun here and we
are a little bit because let's be
honest, CBS is about to just become God
only knows. I mean, it's going to be
number one,
uh, it's [__] TV, so they're all
they're going to talk about is gender
goblinism, and then they're going to
talk about Israel. Most likely, that's
what it's going to oscillate. It's going
to oscillate between, uh, somebody in
the on the girls swim team has a [__]
uh, which is their big issue, and then
also, hey, how good of a job is
Netanyahu doing? Good or great, what say
you? You know, so you're going to have
all of those debates, you know, uh how
best to kill a Palestinian, how does it
is it should it be quick? We don't know.
So, you're going to have all of that at
uh CBS News.
CBS News. Very interesting that the
establishment is now, you know, Barry
Weiss was somebody who was like way
outside the mainstream. She worked at
the New York Times and then laughed,
right? Because like they went they went
super woke and she was like persona non
gratada and she then launched her own
thing and she's very independent in this
in in the sense that she wasn't linked
to you know Viacom or or you know AP
associated press or any of these these
uh conglomerates these big uh media
companies. So she started the free
press, but she had a lot of backing. She
had a lot of financiers come in that
backed her very early on with a lot of
money that that pumped her up and she
created the free press. Again, full
disclosure, I've done events with them.
They've paid me very well one time and
I've done events with them and I I enjoy
her and uh I think she's uh charming and
smart. I is Barry Weiss interested in a
unbiased
look at the Middle East. Uh
[Music]
I don't know. Maybe not. Maybe not.
Perhaps not.
And I think that maybe that's what's
bothering the staffers at CBS because
CBS is an old Now you remember who
watches CBS.
People that watch CBS their entire night
is getting from the kitchen to the
chair. The entire night of an average
viewer of CBS is getting from the
kitchen to the chair. They make a plan
to get from the kitchen to the chair.
They walk into the kitchen. They're in
the kitchen. They find some type of food
that they believe their system can still
handle after all of these years. They
eat a little bit of that food and then
they migrate. It's migration. It's like
it's like a refugee uh you know coming
from Cuba to Florida except they're just
trying to get to their chair in their
living room and then they turn on the
CBS evening news. Okay, again the median
age of a prime time viewer of CBS is
67.8
almost 68 years old but by the way
that's the median. So, we know that
there's far older as well. And the
people that are watching CBS are elderly
people who are they kind of don't know
what's going on. Let's be honest. So, I
think maybe they're trying to bring in
Barry to like make it young and hip.
They're trying to like she's going to
like jazz it up and make it like younger
and hipper and like cooler and whatever.
And then also provide the old people the
content they want, you know, which is uh
uh, you know, predominantly fear-based
and misleading. And as long as the
content remains uh fear-based and
misleading,
um, it will be good content and they
will eat it up uh, until they go on that
final pilgrimage to wherever. But we we
congrats to Barry. a great gig. Uh CBS
is an old clunker of a car. Nobody who's
young respects it. Nobody's getting
their news anymore from cable that is
under 40. Uh nobody is reading these
papers anymore half the time. I read
them because I have this dumb show. Uh
most people are getting their news
directly now from a person who's being
bombed. That's who's the news is now.
The news is directly from someone who's
literally being bombed at the moment.
Like there is no more article about the
bombing. Someone whose family just got
incinerated in a fire is on a phone
telling you what happened. Please help
me. Help me.
So there's not a ton of editorializing
to be done now. We're just getting it
directly from the horse's mouth. like
the people that are being skinned alive
in their homes, burnt to death, heads
exploding,
uh uh in a a kind of a hurricane of fire
in an inferno, skin melting, eye sockets
out. Those are the people that are now
on the phone telling you what your
government is funding.
Okay. So, that's even I got to get rid
of this cuz it's even um it's kind of
it's kind of bothering my neck even.
And I feel like I feel like with the
beard, it feels anti-Semitic. Um but but
it's not. It's actually, by the way,
here's what's funny about this whole
thing. Truly, this is actually funny.
It's actually funny. There's nothing
less anti-Semitic than this than what
I'm doing. stacking two bagels to uh
represent the Twin Towers, having manage
it twine, and dressing in this costume
is actually the least anti-Semitic thing
anyone has ever done. So, but and that
and that's what's funny about the world
is you see it and immediately go, "Oh my
god, I bet that's so rat. That's
offensive and crazy." But this is the
type of thing the free press should be
defending, right? We hope the free press
is defending this and sharing this clip.
We imagine the free press will be
sharing this clip. Yes. Yes. Or yes.
Laughing at life is easier when you
actually feel good. Between processed
foods, environmental toxins, and the
stress of just existing in today's
world, feeling run down has become the
norm. But your body wasn't meant to feel
this way. Armor colostrum is nature's
original superfood. Packed with over 400
bioactive nutrients that fortify gut
health, supercharge immunity, fuel
stamina, revitalize hair growth, and
help you function at your best once
again. Because keeping up with the chaos
of modern life is a lot more fun when
you have the energy to do it. We worked
out a special offer for my audience.
Receive 30% off your first subscription
order. Go to armor.com/tim or enter tim
to get 30% off your first subscription
order. That's a rm.comtim.
That's a rm.comtim.
But the news now has gone from like a
guy and he'd be sitting at a desk and
he'd be a good-looking guy like David
Mure. get up the picture of David Mure
because he's a hottie and he and he's
not purely white. There's something else
going on and you kind of imagine him at
a bar and he's having a glass of scotch
and then a woman walks in maybe like a
Katherine Zeta Jones back in the day,
not now. I know she's older now. And
David Mure is at a bar and he's that
type of guy that you imagine nailing
like a Hollywood A-lister. He's just a
good-looking guy and he has that face
that seems like he cares. And then that
guy would get on the news and he would
go, "The continued conflict in the
Middle East has been incredibly deadly
and unfortunate." And the people in
their houses would go, "Yeah, yeah, well
that sucks.
That's tough." You know, that's a sad
thing.
And now, but you're removed. You're kind
of removed from it because you don't
really know what's going on. And then
they'd show like a few they'd show some
bombs. There'd be some lights. There'd
be some things going on and off. And
you'd go, "Yeah, that's bad." And then
he'd go, "The terrorism that is being p,
you know, like uh the terrorist." And
they would say that word a lot. They
would be like, "The terrorism and the
terror." And then you go, "Right, right,
right. Terrorists." Yeah. Got to root
them out. Get them. Smoke them out of
their hole. Remember all the George W.
Bush got to smoke them out of their
hole. Get them. Got them good. Get them.
Root them out. Bush was the first one
after this whole thing happened. He
goes, "They're going to have to do some
things, not be too nice." George W. Bush
came out was like, "Yeah, I I'm no fan
of terrorists." And he's like, "They're
going to have to go into these places
and it's not because it's guerrilla
warfare." And listen, some of that is
understandable, inevitable. We get it.
It is not nice. You know, guerrilla
warfare, warfare in cities is not
pretty. The Pentagon's planning, by the
way, if you read what the Pentagon's
planning, they're planning to have it uh
here.
Uh so, and it's not nice. And they're
planning actually to have it here. The
Pentagon for many, many years has been
looking at what happens when the
population just gets a little too
excited. Um but you would have a guy
like David Mure and he'd be out there
and there'd be this filter and you would
be understanding what's happening in a
geopolitical context, right? A
geopolitical context. like you'd be
understanding like um that there are uh
things that are uh beyond our
understanding that can't really be
uh you know fleshed out fully here.
We're just going to use words that give
you the idea that uh it's it's it's uh
terrible and unfortunate and it's a
prolonged that's one of the prolong it's
a prolonged conflict. It's a terrorism
and extremism, radical extremism,
radical terrorism, extremism, prolonged
conflict, conflicts, terrorism,
civilians, sadly, death, you know, and
all of these things. And it just kind
and again, you're 70, you're watching,
you're watching the news, you know what
I mean? The pills kicking in and you're
you're coming back and forth. There's a
piece of pie that's lodged in your
esophagus that isn't going down. It's
breaking down in the lower range of your
esophagus. So, you're breathing through
the pie and you're going
[Music]
[Applause]
and then intermittently David Mure's
coming in and explaining Gaza to you.
And that's used that was the news. Now
the news is your your your daughter
comes home
because nobody used to care about
anything by the way. Kids didn't care
about anything ever. No one cared about
anything. I was a child. No one really
cared. Nobody was in engaged.
16-year-old girls were not screaming
about
uh colonialism
in in 1997. That's not what was going
on. But now, how you get the news is
your daughter comes in and she's really
upset about something she saw on Tik Tok
and then she goes, "Look at this." And
then she hands you the phone and then
you're watching there's a girl on TikTok
and she's like standing on a mound of
rubble. Okay. And she's going, "My
family was burned. They were burned
alive.
Can you come get me? My family was
burned."
And and and then you have to explain to
your daughter, you got to go, "Honey,
there's always people being burned alive
in our world." What do you mean, honey?
You're so lucky. That's why I tell you
to never complain about anything. You're
so lucky to get on a bus in our little
little, you know, Pacific Northwest
suburb with our crisp air and our alpine
lakes and you're so lucky to get on a
bus and go to a school and have your
biggest problem be that Sarah doesn't
want to be friends with you anymore. I
tell you, friendships, they change.
People grow apart and then sometimes
they reconnect later on. Remember when
we had that talk? You're so lucky that
that's your biggest problem because
there's many people your age that are
being burned alive right now in their
homes. They're being burned alive in
their homes and they're watching their
parents burn. And the thing about uh
fire is that you can you scream while
you're being burned. Honey, this is
something that people don't realize, but
actually while you're engulfed in
flames, you are still screaming and you
can still hear it. And it's a terrible
way to die, to be burned alive while you
still scream. And that's happening all
over the world all the time. And honey,
and and why is it happening? Why can't
it stop? Why are we funding it? Why
don't you care? Hey, hey, calm down. The
world is very complicated and very big.
It's a big world. The world is very big.
And in a big complicated world where
there's lots of different people, some
of them are going to burn each other
alive.
Some of them are going to cook each
other in pots and there's just not much
we can do about it. But what I'd like
you to do is is is stop getting so upset
about it. And then they go they this is
why they had to ban Tik Tok. They don't
care about your kids' mental health, by
the way. They don't. All they give them
is poison little waffle bites. I mean,
that's all children are given from the
time in this country they're three until
they hit puberty, which they're now
hitting at like 10, by the way. Like,
kids are going through puberty. Women
are fully pregnant at 12 years old,
smoking sigs on welfare. And and it's
because they're eating these little
these little waffle these little waffle
bites and little pancake crisps and all
kinds of weird fruity dinner. And you
know what they really are is little
[__] bites because because it does
change, you know, and people become
trans from the breakfast cereal. They
have uh you know the thing with the you
know uh Count Choulcula and then the
smacks that frog all of these things. So
all so these kids are poisoned with
little uh you know French toast uh uh
you know hot fudge uh sundae little uh
you know they they they'll put like a
little like some type of like uh uh
little mini cake and then that becomes a
cereal like a you know right right
common sweeteners may be accelerating
puberty in kids yeah whatever it's not a
science show I'm not going to go into
the whole thing here but my point is
that all of these sugars cereals drive
your kids insane. They spike their
insulin. They crash. And God, and but by
the way, anyone who's genuinely trans,
you know, we obviously love and support
you. Look at me. I'm literally
identifying as a rabbi right now. But,
you know, I think, you know, there's a
lot of like, hey, a little social
contagion. I want to be cool, too. Which
is fine. Um, and and and and not for
every it's more the women that are doing
that. The women, the trans women, the
dudes who want to be women are I kind of
more legit. And then also like some of
the women who want to be men are clearly
legit. But I just say, "Hey everyone,
let's not do the hormones early. Let's
just wait a little bit until we're
totally sure. Totally certain. And then
you do you. I don't care. It doesn't
matter." Um, but so, but we don't care
about your kids' mental health. We would
not feed them the food we do if we cared
about their mental health. We never
would do that. we wouldn't, you know,
the diet of uh everything they get
really in this country, the pressure
that's put on them. All these kids that
have to get into Ivy League schools,
some of them kill themselves. There was
a school in LA, Harvard Westlake. These
kids were under so much pressure to get
into top colleges that they I believe
they hung themselves or one of them
might have shot themselves. I'm just
saying how terrible it is, the pressure
that is put on children in this country
to excel. Now, the opposite of that is
my fat, useless parents putting no
pressure on me to do anything. Also not
good, by the way. Footnote, but I'm just
saying we don't care about the kids'
health. The reason that we wanted to ban
TikTok had nothing to do with bullying
and it had nothing to do with mental
health. It was the fact that kids were
starting to look at the world and go,
why is this like this? Why are we why is
this happening? Why is everybody getting
killed? And then parents had to have
these really uncomfortable conversations
with their children about the fact that
hey, it's just part of the game. It's
part of the game. It's part of the game.
So then they had to ban Tik Tok, which
didn't work, but there they did try and
who knows it may soon work. We don't
know. But I'm telling you right now, you
had two tragic years at LA's most elite
private school at Harvard Westlake. Four
students, two alumni, and one parent
have all taken their own lives. And
that's very sad. All right, I don't want
to read the article, but I am I'm not
lying to you. It's true. And a lot of
these people are taking their own lives
because they're under pressure to
succeed and to excel. And we do that to
children, whether it's in sports,
whether it's in academics. So, we're not
a country that prioritizes anybody's
mental health. Nobody's. Not adults. Not
adults.
not adult. We don't prioritize anybody's
mental health. We don't. We never have.
We don't. So, anytime somebody goes,
"Actually, we got to start thinking
about the mental health." There's
another agenda. It's easy to see.
There's actually another agenda. Does
this come across as anti-Semitic with
the curls? I'm only wondering with the
curls because this is how the costume
came at Spirit Halloween. Many people
ask me all the time about online
businesses and online commerce,
e-commerce. Most people ask me about
this when they're down on their luck.
People that are suffering from food
insecurity or houselessness will often
ask me about ecommerce and online
activity. Can I get a can I run a
business online is what many of them
will say. And I will tell them
absolutely you can. The biggest issue
that most online businesses have, okay,
is scaling. How do you scale? And I
explain this to people. I I go out in
the streets to missions to all these
different places. And I explain this to
people. And ShipStation is the answer
because users of ShipStation report
scaling three times faster than average,
allowing them to reinvest more into
their business with the time and money
that they are saving. Okay. ShipStation
allows you to automate shipping tasks
and manage orders in an easytouse
dashboard. I'm telling you, I love
ShipStation because I've seen friends go
from fledgling mom and pop businesses to
literally some of the largest companies
you'll ever see using ShipStation
because they can ship. I have a friend
that makes little uh duads and
knickknacks for the holidays and ships
them to people and people love them
because they're made with care. Okay?
They're not made in China with
communism. They're made by people in
America who sit in their homes and make
the little little
pieces. And maybe it'll be a maybe it'll
be an animal on a frozen lake or pond.
Or maybe it'll be a a a tree.
Whatever it is, maybe it's a little
turkey. Gobble gobble. What it is, you
These are the little knick-knacks. When
you walked in your grandmother's house
when you were young and she would have
these little knick-knacks, you
understood what life was about. Okay.
Now everything is cold and modern. It's
like a neurologist's office. And you
walk into a holiday and it looks like
someone's going to tell you you have a
tumor because there's nothing in
anyone's home. Everything is about
finishes. Slate gray, black, satanic
stone. Reminds you of Mordor. Okay. It
reminds you of the ring. It reminds you
of uh of of power. Okay. Um you look at
the way these homes are designed and the
way these kitchens are designed. And the
theme of a lot of these homes is the
only god is death. And that is not what
we're trying to do here. We want to have
an e-commerce business with little
knickknacks, little things. You could
ship them out. Little fun things, little
uh, you know, misery all the penguins
face to, you know, having these little
ceramic things in a house makes a family
mean something. Okay. And my friend has
this little business where they'll make
something fun and they ship it. And they
use Ship Station because it allows them
to centralize label printing, order
management, tracking, returns, and
inventory in one easy to use platform.
So you don't have to manage your back
office. your back office is being
managed for you. It's being automated.
It's it's kind of amazing. And then you
can can also sell the little things that
you do. It's so important to to have
these things in your home. People call
them clutter. That's what people We had
a lot of these anti-lutter shows like
that Japanese woman Marie Condo and uh
Hoarders where they found the most
extreme examples of clutter basically
people that had mental problems and they
said, "Oh, we should clean them out."
And the result of this has been the
destruction of culture in America.
Little by little, trinket by trinket.
Fun little ashtray from Key West gone.
Okay. Little snow globe from Vegas gone.
We call them clutter, but they're
kitschy little knickknacks that used to
fill our lives with pride and joy. Okay.
Um, and you used to be able to say, "We
went on a trip and we got this little
ashtray. We got a fun little whatever.
We got a mug." Okay. Now you go to
Anguila with your friends and the only
thing you could say is, "Oh, we got away
with that uh girl we murdered. Hey, we
murdered a girl and we got away with it
because her body went out to sea." Thank
god the tides went that way. She didn't
wash back up. Okay.
But there was one time in this country
when you would go and you would drive
somewhere in a Winnebago and get fun
knickknacks. Okay. You didn't go with
your boss to Anguila and your friend and
break a woman's neck and then put her in
the ocean and then the tides brought her
out to sea because it was some type of
riptide event. And then her body was
eaten by sharks and it didn't wash up on
the beach because if it did there would
have been DNA tests and they would have
called you back there and it would have
been a whole big thing. But it wasn't.
Okay. But that's not the way it used to
be. You used to walk in on Thanksgiving
and there'd be a little table in the
living room with knick-knacks and
trinkets from fun little places and a
lot of them were religious.
A lot of them were religious. and these
little knick-knacks and trinkets and fun
little baskets with little robins's eggs
and little birds and little animals,
little cute little ceramic foxes and
maybe a little guy playing a fiddle.
That was better, okay, than going to
Anguila and committing a murder. You
murdered someone on a beach, okay?
Whether it was an accident or not, and I
don't buy that it was an accident. You
did it. You did it. And it'll haunt you.
And you see her face every time you
close your eyes.
You can also automate repetitive or
tedious tasks to save time and reduce
errors because there are so many errors
that uh you make when you are just
focusing on the most important part of
your business which is the origination
of uh leads and the sales. Sales is the
engine of any business. Sales and
marketing content is king. Marketing is
queen. Gary Vanerchuk, Gary Vee,
actually. Um, what I'm saying is that
there's a revolution happening. A return
to clutter, a return to stuff, a return
to things, a return to uh momentos, a
return to memorabilia. And I think a lot
of this is very good and and very
positive. And I think that if people
don't start embracing things like this,
okay, it's going to be a very we're
going to live in a very empty clinical
hellscape
where people are just literally going to
islands and murdering people and getting
away with it. Okay. Um, upgrade to
shipping software that does more than
keep up with your business. ShipStation
propels it forward. Start your 60-day
free trial at shipstation.com and use
code timill. and that shipstation.com
code Tim Dylan. But my point is this, if
we had Tik Tok during the Iraq war,
kids would have been going nuts. You,
you know, people were flipped out during
the Iraq war and they were only watching
that heavily edited cable news. We had
the internet but it was you weren't get
you know there were documentaries made
but you weren't getting that live up
tothe- minutee live feed of what was
going on in the world right now you were
confronted with every horror. So there
is no more news. Here's my point. This
is the point. There's always a point.
Actually there is. There's no more news.
The news doesn't exist. The news doesn't
really exist anymore.
Everything is pretty accessible now. You
can watch the speeches being given by a
lot of the people that are making news.
You can watch a war zone on your phone.
Does it look like they're avoiding
civilian casualties? You know what I
mean? All of this is very
accessible to you and you can see it and
go, "Huh,
there is no news." Doesn't really matter
what Barry Weiss does with the the CBS.
Doesn't really matter. These
institutions are done. We are getting it
direct from the source. Now, we're
getting it directly from the regions of
the world that it is happening. That
doesn't mean we're not subject to
misinformation and AI and eventually
deep fakes and all of that. Obviously,
we are. But you have more information
now, raw information
in your hand than you've ever had
before. Children that are growing up
right now are never going to go back to
watching the CBS Evening News.
They're never going to go back to
watching the CBS Evening News. God bless
the Ellison's and Paramount and whoever.
It's just a dying brand. It's a
dinosaur. The medium is crumbling. They
have lost the public. And more
importantly, they've lost young people
completely because young people are
realizing they're being propagandized at
a level that older people gladly
accepted. It was normal. It was fine.
Older people were okay with being
propagandized as long as they got a few
things out of it. The young people are
getting nothing out of it. Wait, you're
lying to us and I can't own a house? I
can barely have a job. I have to be
forced into the gig economy. I get to
deliver burritos and I have to listen to
this [__] and I have to pretend that
this is all real and I can't afford
frozen yogurt with my girlfriend and I
have to go along with this horseshit and
I have nothing and no money for it. If
you're doing something you want to get
something out of it. If you were going
to delude yourself and believe the
[__] on the news, you have to get a
little bit out of it. And what Americans
got for many years was a patch of dirt,
a little driveway, and a chance. They
don't have any of that anymore. We've
taken that all away from them. We've
pushed them into a gig economy. We've
pushed them into the hellscape of rent
that goes up every single year. And the
propaganda is actually getting worse.
It's getting more disconnected from
reality, more Orwellian. were asking
them to believe crazier and crazier
things and taking away the little bit
that most people had. People don't want
to be billionaires. People want a house,
a family, a little retirement plan, some
money in the bank if there's an
emergency. They want health care. They
want some kind of steady job. They want
a community with people that share their
values. They're getting none of that
right now. They're getting none of that.
They're getting Chris Jenner's third
head. Chris Jenner has a third head. and
everybody's excited by them. People will
tell you, the people that don't have any
of those things will tell you that they
like Chris Jenner's new head or they're
excited that Taylor Swift, a
billionaire, is going to marry Travis
Kelce, the man who was birthed by Fizer.
And people have to live vicariously now
through that. Why are the kids turning
on the engines of propaganda? Number
one, they're too smart. The technology
is there. They know they're being lied
to. Here's number two. You're you're
taking all of the things away from them
that this entire system was supposedly
purportedly
set up to help them achieve. So, if I'm
a member of the ruling class, I'm I'm
going, "What are we doing here? What
exactly is happening? Uh, we're asking
these people to believe this [__]
that Jeffrey Epste is just like a weirdo
rich guy. No one else did anything wrong
and we don't have any of the files and
the videos aren't real. It's actually
nothing. Nothing happened. Everything's
fine. He never had any relationship with
our intelligence agency or another
intelligence agency. He had no
relationships with anybody. Nobody did
anything.
He was just a weird rich guy. Don't
worry about it. We're asking people to
believe all of this stuff and telling
them. And the reward for that,
the reward for that, okay, is to deliver
a Caesar salad to someone.
That's the reward. Your job now is to
deliver a Caesar salad. Not not that it
would have been right to buy the
[__] anyway, even if you had the
things. But I'm just telling you how the
country ran for a hundred years.
That's what I'm telling you. I'm not
saying it was morally correct to go,
I'll take the house and the car and you
[__] kill everybody. I'm telling you
that's how it worked. That's how the
country ran for ever.
You shut your mouth and I don't want to
get into that. I don't know. Yeah, it's
a government lab. Kids are disappearing.
Shut up. Eat your lasagna. Your mother
made lasagna.
That's the way it worked.
Now everybody's uh, you know, I in a
broken home trying to get some job as a
personal assistant uh, you know, for
some woman who who's on her third head.
So, you're scrging around your car to
find change to get Dell Taco and you're
getting a call from a woman who's
bandaged up because she has her third
head and she's asking you to go to the
pharmacy for her and get the injection
she needs to inject into her face so
that it doesn't fall off.
And then you're going on your phone and
all you hear is, "Help me. I'm being
burned. My family is being burned. Why
are you doing this to me? Why are you
burning me?
Do you see how it's an unsustainable
model? Do you see that? Do you
understand that? Am I Am I completely
You know what's interesting about these
Trader Joe's bagels? They look better
than you think they would.
They actually aren't
911.
Not good.
I'm an alcoholic unless I would try the
wine.
Prize picks run your game. Prize picks
run your game. Prize Picks. Run your
game. This episode is brought to you by
Prize Picks. You and I make decisions
every day, but on prize picks, being
right can get you paid. Don't miss any
of the excitement this season on prize
picks. When it's good to be right, I
mean, the football season's coming up.
You got to get ready for the season. And
you've got to get your bank account
ready for the holidays. How do you do
two things at once? Okay, I'll tell you
right now. It's going to be so much fun.
You got to download the prize picks app.
It's a simple way to play. Just pick
more or less on two to six player stat
projections. Okay. Saquan Barkley more
or less than one rushing TDs. Joe Burrow
more or less than two and a half passing
yards. Josh Allen more or less than 270
passing yards. Folks, it's so easy.
Prize picks is also the best way to get
action on sports in more than 40 states,
including California, Texas, and
Georgia. They put their users first, so
all withdrawals are fast, safe, and
secure. Price offers Venmo, Apple, Pay,
Mastercard, and more for quick, and easy
deposits into your account this football
season. Download the app today and use
code TAM to get $50 in lineups after you
play your first $5 lineup. That's code
TM to get $50 in lineups. After you play
your first $5 lineup prize picks, it's
good to be right. I just went through a
process with trying to help my friend
get an apartment. Credit is so
important, folks. I'm telling you right
now, if you're struggling with credit,
use this use this service. Let's be
honest, when your credit is not in great
shape, it can feel like the whole system
is working against you. You could be
smart with your money, pay your bills,
do everything right, and still get
penalized. In fact, drivers with low
credit scores end up paying 118% more on
full coverage auto insurance than those
with excellent credit. But that's where
Kickoff comes in. It's a smarter, faster
way to start building real credit
without the usual headaches. I'm telling
you, I discovered Kickoff and it was so
good. I recommended it to my friend with
credit problems, and he's doing much
better now. Users with credit under 600
crew an average of 84 points in their
first year with on-time payments. With
transparent, affordable plans starting
at just $5 a month, no hidden fees and
zero interest. Kickoff helps you score
big when it all comes to credit. It's
simple. You make on-time payments.
Credit bureaus see good behavior and
your credit can grow fast. It's so
affordable and easy and effective.
That's what I like about it. It's
affordable, easy, and effective. Many
things are just affordable and easy and
not effective. Some things are effective
and easy but not affordable. Some things
are affordable and effective but not
easy. Some things are effective,
affordable, and easy, but they support
international terrorist organizations.
So, when it's affordable, easy, and uh
you know, it's good. Start building
credit with Kickoff today and you can
get your first month for as little as
$1, that's 80% off the normal price. You
go to getoff.comtim
today. geki koff.comtim.
Can Okay. Must sign up via
getkickoff.com to activate offer. Offer
applies to new kickoff. Customers first
month only. Subject to approval. Offer
subject to change. Average first year
credit score impacted plus 84 points.
Vantage score three between January 2023
and January 2024. For kickoff credit
account users who started with a score
below 600 who paid on time and who had
no delinquencies or collections added to
their credit profile during the period.
Late payments may negatively impact your
credit score. Individual results may
vary.
But my point is this and again nothing
about this suggests cultural
insensitivity. I hope it doesn't. It's a
costume sold. It's I was trying to get a
Shrimal actually. I was trying to get a
Shrimal and I called very connected
people very high up and unfortunately
because it's Saturday and it's what do
they call it? Shabbat. I couldn't get a
Shrimal. So I'm in my car and we pulled
over. I was with a friend of mine and
then we're going through this very uh
orthodox area of Los Angeles and um yes,
go go make it big.
That's how I was going to show up here.
That's exactly what I was going to do,
but we couldn't. So, we had to go to
[__] Spirit Halloween. You'd think
I'd be past this in my career, but I'm
not. And I'm making an important point
about the global nature of whatever.
Here's the point. We're in my car. We're
driving through a Los Angeles, a very
orthodox area, and there was what were
they 15 or 16?
Yeah. There was a bunch of kids running
around uh in the garb. So, we pull over
the the rolly and I said, and it's
Jewish kids, so you know, obviously it's
weird to just talk to random children,
right? It's odd. Obviously, not for
everyone in our country.
Okay. Um but we we I I say, "Come here."
I call them over. And I I called them
over and I said, 'Hey, what's up? Uh,
can I ask you a question? They go,
"Yeah." I go, "The hat, the Shrimal. Uh,
could I get one?" And they go, "Hey,
man." They go, "We're not that sect."
They go, "Are you Jewish?" I go, "No,
but my car is." And they laughed. It got
a laugh. And then I said, "I'm a
comedian." And and I I want a Shrimal
for something I'm doing. They go,
"What's your name?" And I go, "Tim
Dylan." He goes, "My mom listens to
you." And I said, "Thank you. Thank you
for the support from all the
communities." And uh and then we joked
around a little bit with them, but then
and they were explaining to us that the
Shrimal is a whole different thing and
it's a lot of money. One of the kids
goes, "It's expensive." And I was like,
"We got it." But beautiful uh
interaction there. And I I believe that
I actually believe in all of the
cultures getting together. I really do.
Um but what I what I'm what I'm what I'm
saying here is that can get this out of
here now, please. I'm just staring at
this picture, the Shrimal, but I do love
the hat. Uh, but we tried to do better
than this, but it at the end of the day,
we had to go to Spirit Halloween and
Bevmo
and um get this little set. But what my
my point here, if there is a point, and
there always is a point, is that
I'm excited to see what Barry does with
uh CBS. I really am. I I'm I'm excited.
I I I I'm excited to see what it what it
is. I'm happy about it. Uh I I hopefully
I will be considered to be a
uh correspondent. I think I have the
look for it. Uh and I I'm very bullish
on the future of at least the next 6
months to a year of whatever train wreck
that will be because down the road it's
all the kids are off. They're turning it
off. All of these people think they can
wrestle
uh younger people back to these
platforms and back to the [__] It's
not going to happen.
It's certainly not going to happen when
none of them uh you know could afford
bottled water. Uh it's certainly not
going to happen. You you can't
impoverish and emiserate and sink a
bunch of people into debt and then say
and hey and we got a bunch of fairy
tales for you all to believe now. And
now it's story time. Hey, you're all
broke. You're all broke and have
nothing. Now it's story time. Now we're
going to tell you how it all works.
Jeffrey Epstein was a magical magician
that lived in a castle. Like you you
can't have people running around
chomping out aderall, staying up till 3
in the morning writing a dissertation on
god knows what to get a meaningless
degree that they have shoved all of
their hopes and dreams into that's going
to result in nothing. They're in
mountains of debt. They're living in a
little complex and they're spending way
too much of their money on rent, car
insurance. They have no health care.
They hope to God nothing happens to
them. They're going to urgent care.
They're buying Zpacks off the street.
And then they're trying to date each
other, trying to find someone to love
and to commit to and have a family with.
It's all very difficult. It's all
incredibly difficult. all the while
being told they're special and unique
geniuses and this entire period of their
life is going to be very valuable to
them when they're incredibly successful.
They can turn around and talk about how
the hard times built character. Um, it's
the motherload, as Cam Harris, our
friend would say, the motherload of bad
ideas,
uh, to tell a bunch of people that they
should spend most of their life being
delusional psychopaths,
hoping,
uh, that things uh, work out.
And I think people are waking up a
little bit and going, that doesn't
really make sense anymore. And I think
some of the stories you're telling me
are also responsible for why I'm in the
position I'm in. People are kind of
waking up to that. They're going, I
think the Epstein thing is a lie, but I
also think the like that I'm going to be
okay is a lie. And if I work hard and
I'm honest is a lie. And if I obey the
rules is a lie. And if I'm respectful of
other people, it's a lie. And if I don't
call things out that are blatantly
obvious to everyone, it's a lie. I think
all of the lies are actually enforcing
all of the other lies and I don't want
to believe any of them and it's
radicalizing quite a few people. Not me.
Look at me. I'm fine. But most people
out there having real problems with
radicalization. I'm seeing this younger
people to the far left, to the far
right, you know, and even worse to
Taylor Swift. That's even more
disturbing. I mean, I've spoken anarchco
communists and Nazis, and there is
nothing more disturbing than talking to
someone who's really, really, really
into Taylor Swift. There's something
very disturbing about that. At least
there's a historical precedent for being
a Stalinist or a Nazi. This [__]
Taylor Swift [__] [__] is absurd.
It's extreme, and there's no way to
contextualize it in a way that makes me
makes me hopeful at all for the future.
Nazis eventually lose. So do communists
historically. Um but these Swifties I
don't know. I don't know that they will
lose. The breed of normie that they
represent I feel is going to do a
tremendous amount of damage and already
is to our society. this breed of white
Converse shoewearing Austin City limits
going
uh uh idiot that runs around
eating caviar and following influencers
and believing that life is about going
on vacations.
These people are going to destroy
civilization at a faster pace than any
of the political radicals in my
estimation. In my estimation, you know,
everybody loves Helix mattresses. When
people come and stay with me, they go,
"Why are these mattresses so good?" And
I go, "Helix?" They go, "Really?" I go,
"Yeah, they ship them right to your door
and they're the best mattresses in the
world." There's nothing worse than
mattress shopping. All those people that
work in those stores are creeps. They're
watching you lay down. Something wrong
with them. Helix is amazing. You could
take a short quiz to find out what kind
of sleeper you are. Are you a side
sleeper, a back sleeper? Do you sleep on
your stomach? Are you a hot sleeper?
What ails you? Sleep is so important.
All the new studies coming out are
saying people that don't sleep are going
cuckoo. And you don't want to be that.
You don't want to be a a cuckoo.
You want to be a person who sleeps, a
nice deep sleep, mountain air, salt air
for the sea. And you sleep in a nice
slumber. And you dream and you have
dreams about walking in the meadow and
it's nice. And if you don't have a nice
mattress, that's not what happens. You
wake up constantly. You're tossing.
You're turning. You're kind of insane.
If you don't really sleep, you're
technically kind of drunk. You're not
getting enough oxygen to your brain.
You're wandering around. You're angry.
You lash out at people sometimes
violently. You are a danger to yourself
and others. You're putting yourself in a
bad position with friends and family. Uh
some people may get in car accidents.
They may be performing tasks with heavy
machinery and injure themsel. They could
be driving a boat and not realize
they're not in enough water and actually
end up uh on kind of a sandbar. All of
this can happen if you're not properly
rested. Helix is here for your sleep.
You can sleep easy no matter what you
did on Helix. You may have killed
someone in a car accident and gotten
away with it. But with a Helix mattress,
you sleep soundly all night. No
problems. Waking up maybe once to use
the restroom, look at yourself in the
mirror and go, I can do this. I can do
it. I'll just get up tomorrow like
nothing happened. If you've killed
someone in a car accident but got away
with it in a hit and run, you need a
mattress that is a good sleeper.
Helix.comtimd
helix.comtimd.
If you've done a horrible thing and you
need to sleep it off, helix
timdillancy.com
for any of your live needs. We're on the
road this fall and then uh this winter
we'll be in uh other places, but we're
getting the hour together in some of the
best clubs in America and then moving on
to theaters. But you can see me uh in
Columbus, Ohio. You could see me uh in
Riad, Saudi Arabia or Abu Dhabi. You
could see me in Oklahoma City. In
Phoenix, Arizona, in Fort Lauderdale, in
Chicago, in San Jose, uh in Salt Lake
City, you could see me uh in Chicago. I
think I said um you can see me as well
in Orange County, California in Brandon.
You can see me in Colorado. Tim Dylan
comedy and Houston timillcomdy.com.
That'll take us through January. That is
uh the rub. Much success to Barry Weiss.
Much success masle
mausle. And we are uh very excited and
hopefully will be chosen as a
correspondent for the reinvention of
CBS. uh uh news and and you know what
this means with Barry taking over CBS uh
the last two words that oxygenarians are
going to say before they collapse into
cardiac arrest on their couch is human
shields. They're going to go they use
them as human shields. What are they
supposed to do?